<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kodaikanal Guide</string>
    <string name="menuThingsToKnow">Things To Know</string>
    <string name="menuGettingThere">Getting There</string>
    <string name="menuMajorAttractions">Major Attractions</string>
    <string name="menuRestaurants">Top Restaurants</string>

    <string name="gettingTherebyBus">By Bus</string>
    <string name="gettingThereByBusDetails">Regular bus services are available
                 from the cities of Chennai, Coimbatore, Pondicherry, Madurai, Trichy and many more.</string>
    <string name="gettingThereByTrain">By Train</string>
    <string name="gettingThereByTrainDetails">Many tourists take the rail route and get down at Kodai Road, which
                 is about 100 kilometres away from the main town. From here,
                you can get a taxi. Being the only mode of transportation from
                Kodai Road to Kodaikanal, taxi rates are not all that negotiable.</string>
    <string name="gettingThereByAir">By Air</string>
    <string name="gettingThereByAirDetails">The airport nearest to Kodaikanal is Madurai, about 120 kilometres
                away. Others in line include the Trichy airport and the Coimbatore airport,
                150 kilometres and 175 kilometres away, respectively. From the airport,
                you can easily get a bus to Kodaikanal.</string>
    <string name="gettingThereBySelfDrive">Road/Self Drive</string>
    <string name="gettingThereBySelfDriveDetails">Kodaikanal is easily accessible by road from Chennai
                (439 kilometres) and Bangalore (305 kilometres). It is only about 3.5
                hours away from Madurai. But if you decide to drive just make sure
                 our fuel tank is full because there are very limited gas stations on the way.</string>

    <string name="thingsToKnow1">Reconfirm with your hotel directly calling at Hotel, if you have
                booked online.</string>
    <string name="thingsToKnow2">If you are driving, make sure you have sufficient fuel when you
                leave Dindigul, because after that , it is difficult to get fuel. You need to climb hill of
                50km, hill climbing may use double the fuel. Make sure you have full tank. Also take some food
                with you if you have babies or you may get hungry. It will take nearly 2 hours to climb the hill. </string>
    <string name="thingsToKnow3">Download google map for offline navigation. Download place
                details also because at some places you may not get sufficient network or internet </string>
    <string name="thingsToKnow4">Public tranport is not good or mostly not available in Kodaikanal.
                You have to make your taxi or join some tourist group via a tour agent. You hotel can do that
                for you"</string>
    <string name="thingsToKnow5">If you are foreigner, keep your passport safe. Mostly, nobody will ask for passport unless
        something wrong happens. Show it only to police personnel. Crime is very less in
                 Kodaikanal but it is better to be safe</string>
    <string name="thingsToKnow6">Self driven cars are not available in Kodaikanal. If you wish a
                 self driven car, take it from Chennai and drive to Kodaikanal. You can take it from
                 ZoomCar, book from their website or App</string>
    <string name="priorityMust">Must</string>
    <string name="prioritySure">Sure</string>
    <string name="restaurantAltafsCafeName">Altafs Cafe</string>
    <string name="restaurantAltafsCafeDetails">A restaurant dealing mainly in Indian and Middle
                 Eastern cuisines for the hungry and tired travelers of Kodaikanal.</string>
    <string name="restaurantPastryCorner">Pastry Corner</string>
    <string name="restaurantPastryCornerDetails">Pick up great picnic sandwiches and yummy muffins
                 and croissants at this highly popular bakery, or squeeze onto the benches with
                a cup to watch the world go by.</string>
    <string name="restaurantAstoria">Hotel Astoria</string>
    <string name="restaurantAstoriaDetails">Crowded with tourists and locals, Astoria is almost
                 impossible to get through during the lunch hours when it serves the
                all-you-can-eat thalis.</string>
    <string name="restaurantPatel">Patel Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurantPatelRestaurantDetails">If you are a Gujarati lusting after excellent
                dishes from your cuisine, Patels is the place to be.</string>
    <string name="attraction1Name">Kodaikanal Lake</string>
    <string name="attraction1Details">Kodai Lake that lays in the heart of Kodaikanal, is a star shaped man made lake
                 that is draped on an area of 60 acres. Boating, horse riding, cycling and angling are a few of the
        adventure activities tourists can appease themselves with, near the lake.</string>
    <string name="attraction2Name">Green Valley View (Suicide Point)</string>
    <string name="attraction2Details">As the name suggest, it offers tourists with amazing view of the plains,
                valleys and hills. Breath taking view of the Vaigai dam makes for an experience worth remembering.
        The green valley View is formerly called as Suicide Point. It received its name because of the dangerous
        valley which is deep and dense. The valley below the point is more than 5000 feet drop. </string>
    <string name="attraction3Name">Pillar Rocks</string>
    <string name="attraction3Details">The famous Pillars Rocks of Kodaikanal are located around 8 km from the lake
        and are an exquisite picnic spot. Constituting of a beautiful mini garden, the place is so named as it has
        three vertically positioned boulders reaching up to a height of 400 feet.</string>
    <string name="attraction4Name">Berijam Lake</string>
    <string name="attraction4Details">An important hill station in not just Tamil Nadu but the whole of India,
                Kodaikanal offers an assortment of picnic spots inclusive of the magnificent
                Berijam Lake.</string>


</resources>
